Hey...
Rin.
Wake up.
Come here.
It was just a dream.
There's nothing to worry about.
Huh?
Bunny Drop
I dunno about tomorrow
It's different than a sacrifice Something's off
I don't think it's like some penalty game
So, why? I don't get it at all.
I'm a little bit unsatisfied, but your presence
right now is more than just important.
There's no such thing in this world
as something never-ending
Crying isn't painful, it's love's sweet drops, sweet drops!
I want to keep dreaming forever, ya know?
I want to be more kind, ya know?
As long as I'm with you, I'm happy
Girls sure are strong, ya know?
But sometimes we're weak, ya know?
Our wish is to be happy, happy, happy!
And those days will be happy, too!
Just wanna make you happy!
I want one too.
Grandpa used to make them!
Is that so?
Hey, I want my own knife.
You're still young...
There are kids' knives!
Seriously?
I'll think about it.
Now hurry and eat.
We gotta get going soon.
Fine.
Isn't that baby cute?
Sure.
I'm Kawachi, Kaga Rin's father's relative.
I'm taking care of Rin right now.
Uh-huh...
Um... You're Yoshii Masako...
Rin's mother, right?
Um...
M-Me?
Uh... Yeah...
I'd like to meet you in person to talk about something.
I don't mind coming to you, so if you'll just pick a place...
A place... Um...
Oh, I don't know... I guess in the shopping area, at the...
You're gonna have to be a bit more specific.
This is so cute!
More crafts, Mom?
You made this flower too?
That's right. It's called embroidery.
Wow! That's amazing!
When you get a little bigger, I'll teach you how to do it.
Really?
Only because you're so clever with your hands, Rin.
So, what's your plan?
I can't say until I meet her...
Keep an eye on Rin while I'm out.
Daikichi...
This is important...
so have a good, long talk with her.
Your mother's been looking forward to spending time with Rin anyway.
This is really close to Grandpa's house...
Welcome!
Are you alone, sir?
One more person is coming afterwards.
Non-smoking, please...
Careful!! You're gonna spill it!
The stress just keeps building...
Believe me, I've been there!
Americano, please.
One Americano!
Would you like anything else?
No, thanks.
This is very nice, Ms. Saionji!
But I'd expect no less from you.
Now you just need to give each character some trauma.
Two or three each is fine.
D-Don't you think that's a bit much?
No, it's just right!
This doesn't make sense...
After going through all the trouble of hiding that she was ever at Grandpa's...
Why stay in the same neighborhood?
I'll see you later, Ms. Saionji.
Thanks for coming.
Pretty careless for someone trying to disappear...
Mama, I have to pee!
Yes, yes. Just hold on for a few minutes.
Hello? Where are you?
I'm already in the restaurant.
S-Souichi...
No. His grandson.
She's like a little kid...
U-Um... I'm sorry about that.
It's just that you look so much like him...
It's fine.
You're not the first.
Now that I have a chance to really look at you,
I think Souichi looked kinder.
Definitely...
I brought a photo of Rin.
Thank you...
It was taken at the beginning of the year.
It's at a rice cake party at her kindergarten.
She looks like a young lady already!
I heard someone call you "Miss" earlier...
W-Were you watching?
But the name was...
It's my pen name.
Sorry...
I'm totally out of it after pulling an all-nighter because of deadline hell...
Hah...?
Is work the reason you left Rin behind?
Um...
And apparently you made Rin think that you were just the housekeeper.
Did you do that ever since she was born?
Mm... My work is the reason...
However, it's also true that I was Souichi's maid.
Even while I was pregnant, though,
I refused to think of Rin as my daughter.
S-Sorry. I'm not sure I understand...
For the longest time, I wasn't popular at all...
Then, just as I was about to finally land a major assignment,
I found out that I was pregnant...
This isn't the kind of work you can do while raising a kid...
but Souichi encouraged me to have the child anyway...
Every day, I'd either work or stay in bed, getting fatter and flabbier...
Even so, strangely enough...
when she was born, she was so cute that I couldn't help but fall in love.
"Strangely enough"...?
That's why, even though I refused to accept her as my daughter,
I tried desperately to balance both work and Rin.
It was tough trying to be a day person...
And sometimes I'd have to go out at night for meetings,
which meant being up late...
It was physically impossible.
Um... I heard that Rin stayed with you in an apartment at night?
That's right...
Did you go out at night then?
Well, it would be really late.
Rin would already be asleep, so I'd go out for a bit...
Sometimes, Souichi would watch her.
Even now, Rin occasionally wakes up after midnight.
How do you think she feels when she finds that she's all alone?
But... how else was I supposed to raise a child on my own?
My grandfather wanted the three of you to be a family, didn't he?
Do you have a problem with me continuing to live with Rin?
No.
I'm not Rin's mother anymore,
I don't have the right to make those kinds of choices.
Even though you were the one who gave birth to her?
Th-That has nothing to do with it!
How do you really feel about Rin?
Isn't she important to you?
I-I don't know...
Um... I just have one favor to ask...
What is it?
When that girl goes to school, please let her use your family name.
What? My family name?
If her surname is different from yours,
I'm sure she'll have a rough time...
Can you just promise me that?
I know where you're coming from, but...
I can't promise that...
She's always been Kaga Rin...
I don't think a person's name is that easy to change...
As a woman, I'm not particularly attached to my family name.
After all, it might change one day...
Rin's a woman as well, so she probably feels the same way.
Yeah, but Rin's six...
And that's not what I'm talking about.
Besides, that's just your opinion!
There's only one thing that's important!
And that's "Rin", the name Souichi gave her.
Now, good-bye.
Look...
I'm a man, so I don't really get what you're saying.
But...
I'll still talk to her.
Talk to her?
You'd make that little girl decide?!
Isn't that cruel?!
I'm...
I'm thinking about what's best for Rin.
Making the decision for her is what would be cruel.
I want to ask Rin how she feels.
After that, the two of us will decide together.
I'll let you know what the answer is later.
It sounds like she's no good!
I'm sure of it!
Who would abandon a cute little girl like that?!
It defies common sense!
Well, she does worry about Rin...
It's just that she's a bit odd.
It's as if she has no idea she's dragging other people into her mess.
What are you talking about?!
Of course, a mother would worry about her daughter!
If she really cared about her, she'd want to see her!
Now, now. We don't know her situation. Have an orange.
What did Grandpa ever see in her?
Well, at this stage, it hardly matters...
The thing is, she demanded that when Rin starts school, she use my surname.
Oh, I agree with that.
A child should definitely have the same family name as her guardian.
Yeah... I understand, but...
How am I supposed to explain that to Rin?
She's already got a name of her own...
She's a girl, so her family name will change when she gets married anyway...
That again?!
What again?
It'll be easier on her if she uses our family name at school.
Better than letting someone tease her for having a different name.
And you think she can keep that all straight?
There's a lot going on, even in elementary school.
I just don't want things to be difficult for her.
What if I adopt Rin?
Wha...?!
As long as she doesn't object...
That way, she really will be Kawachi Rin...
Yeah, that way's more natural...
This isn't a decision you can make so thoughtlessly!
I'm not being thoughtless!
This is something that had to happen, right?!
We were going to have to go through this sooner or later!
Easy, easy...
It's not all the same!
Yes, it is! It absolutely is!
I'm not passing the baton to anyone else.
That would be the worst thing I could do to Rin.
If it's for Rin, I'll do whatever it takes.
Here.
This is for me?
Yep, it's yours.
But you can only use when I'm next to you, got it?
If you promise me that, you get to use the knife.
I promise!
As thanks, I'll make curry for you!
Seriously?
Tonight!
How about tomorrow...?
I forget.
Do I push or pull?
Wait a sec.
Give it here...
Like this, 'kay?
Daikichi, you're good at that!
Yeah, well, I've been alone for a long time...
Now you try.
Do it nice and slow...
Don't drink the bathwater.
I won't.
Go down to your shoulders and count to ten.
'Kay.
One...
One, two...
two, three...
three, four, shut the door...
five, six, pick up sticks, seven...
four, five, six...
Daikichi, you're counting too slowly!
Don't eat too quickly.
Okay.
Hey, Rin...
What?
Nevermind...
Your curry's delicious!
Do I have to do it as long as you do?
Oh, no... It's fine...
Mm... You know...
I'm not your father...
I know.
But I'm not your big brother either, right?
Nobody thinks that!
I'm just saying!
What I want to know is, what am I then?
Daikichi!
That's my name...
Listen, and this is only if you aren't against it...
What I'm trying to say... How can I put it...?
Uh... What do you...
Rin, what would you think...
about me becoming your real father?
Daikichi, you...
become my father?
So if we did that, your name would become Kawachi Rin...
Kawachi... Rin.
No.
No...?
Don't you think it'd be better if you had a father?
My father is Grandpa.
My name is Kaga Rin and I like it.
It's the same name as Grandpa.
That's important.
I see...
Daikichi should just stay Daikichi.
Daikichi?
What's wrong?
Are you crying?
This is sweat!
It's only March...
Oh, shut up!
Just open your mouth!
It was open, but you were crying!
I said I wasn't crying!
Move your head up a little more...
'Kay...
Y'know, this'll always be your home...
Yeah.
We mustn't forget what we believe.
Because the morning will surely come.
We mustn't lose our dreams.
Because one day they will surely come true.
The first step... step to tomorrow...
Starting today, everything will be new!
Build that courage up, nice and big...
and take that first step out!
I see.
You're gonna get fat, you know...
That's fine. I'm worthless anyway.
Gimme one.
Screw off.
A sunny early Sunday afternoon
Let's go somewhere today
It's the same road I'm used to traveling
But I can see it sparkling so bright
With the sun shining down its warmth
And you here by my side...
I'm already high, high, high
I feel like dashing out
Sing, la, la, la
My voice out to forever
I'm already high, high, high
Ride the dancing wind
Sing, la, la, la
My voice springs up
Only babies are held like that!
That's what Sayaka said!
What?! That's not true!
There are times when even adults want to be held in someone's arms.
Adults?! Why?!
I don't know either.
Is it still okay to be held, even after I'm a first-grader?
Of course!
I'll hold you no matter how old you are...
W-What?!
I'm sorry.
I should've held you before.
What?
I'll hold you next time you cry, Daikichi.
Hold on, now...
Don't worry!
Am I raising Rin or is she raising me?
I have to wonder sometimes...